Good morning those a part of the rarity
nation. Your absolute most genuine queen
is back again with another vlog. Today
me and the girls are checking into a
best western hotel for a little societal
detox. Say something nice. Twilight
dear. She's just shy. Anyways, about the
societal detox capitalism. Who's that? I
don't know
her. Fluttershy, you disgusting heathen.
Control your behind. I'm on live right
now to my tens of followers. Oh, so you
think just because you're both white and
a unicorn, you can't tell me what to do.
I never said anything of the sort, even
if both those cases are true and in fact
do give me utmost authority to do what I
want. But you implied it like you always
do. Don't point that camera at my face.
Um, I can do what I want because I'm a
white woman. Damn, Fluttershy, that fart
you did is stinking it up back here.
What have you been eating? Oatmeal.
Where's Pinkie Pie and Applejack? We're
back here. Yo, where? Celestia put us in
the trunk. Oh my god, you're in the
trunk. But there aren't any seat belts
in there. Well, we can't exactly fit all
five of us back here with how fat all of
our ass cheeks are.
Pinkie Pie, stop farting in here.
There's nowhere for you to run,
Applejack. Uh-oh, here it comes again.
Applejack,
do you dare me to do it again?
Applejack, Applejack, wake up. Turn
right at the next exit and you should
see the hotel. Twilight, I know where
I'm going. Who's the Uber driver here?
Why did you even take a job as an Uber
driver when you're the princess of
Equestria? What? As princess am I not
allowed to try new things?
You missed the exit. [__] I told you to
turn right. Well, maybe I would have if
you weren't talking to me. I need to
back up, but my ethereal hair is
clouding my vision of the mirror. Can
you look through the back window and
tell me if some pony is behind us? Yeah.
Yeah. As in you can do that for me or
Yeah. As in there's some pony behind us.
A pony is behind us. Tell me when
they're gone.
They're gone now. Aren't you going to
go? How do I go backwards? Put the car
in park and then drive in reverse.
Twilight, I'm a god, but I'm still just
a pony. You're going to have to explain
how to do those things in more simpler
terms. I don't know if I can. The word
reverse is already as simple as it gets.
Wait, she's coming
back. You just ran some pony over. Which
one? Derpy hooves. That's fine. Disabled
ponies waste far too many resources. You
know what? I'm getting out. Since we're
close enough to the hotel, I can just
walk. I'm going to go up to the
receptionist with my cool new Dora. the
explorer suitcase and check on our
reservations. If everything's good, I'll
wave to you girls from the front door.
Then you can start bringing in our bags.
You know, you could have just gone up
there and done it instead of explain it
to us. Oh my god, Twilight, you're being
annoying. Just go stop wasting our time.
Can you like
stop? I'm sorry. We have to clean that
glass every time some pony walks
through.
Now we have to like clean it even more.
Are you mentally challenged? I said I'm
sorry. And I said you're like mentally
challenged. I'm here to check in. I made
a reservation.
Obviously. Why else would you be here,
you weirdo? What's your name, bubble
[__] Twilight
Sparkle. Ew, that sounds like a stupid
name. Did your parents like hate you?
I'll like see if you got a reservation.
Just hold your ass tight.
You know, I'm like here with my friends.
We're all staying in the same room
together. I know it sounds weird, but we
really are that close. Is it like a sex
thing? No. No. No. Nothing like that.
We're taking a societal detox. Do you
know what that is? I like Don't really
care, [__] A societal detox is when
you take a break from social pressures
like work, school, all that [__] to
focus on your mental health and
relationships. It's literally the only
cure for this capitalist hellcape we
live in. Like, have you ever woke up and
you're just like, "Ugh, why do I have to
participate in society today?" No. Yeah.
That's your body begging for a detox.
Can you like stop talking? Here's your
key card. Don't shove it up your ass.
Now, why in Celestia would I ever do
that? I don't know. With how much [__]
you just spewed, I figured you had room
for more [__] to fit up there. The [__]
is waving. Let's make like a bundle of
bananas and peel out.
Hey, Rarity. I saw you were filming for
your YouTube channel. Oh, yeah. Do you
think I, you know, could maybe be in it?
I don't know. I'm your Uber driver.
Surely I should show up somewhere near
the beginning.
Let me out. This is an unjust citizen's
arrest. I don't have to listen to you.
I'm both white and an ollie cornorn.
Give me five stars before you get out. I
was going to, but probably not now that
you locked me in here. Rarity, please
just let me have this. Okay, fine. Wait,
turn your phone this way so I can watch
you while you do it.
Hey, before we get ourselves settled in,
does anybody want to play the elevator
game? Though what now? The elevator
game. It's super spooky fun. Do we have
to? We're losing social detox time. Come
on, Twilight. It'll be really fun. Fine,
waste everyone's time. I'll just stand
here calculating how many IQ points were
collectively losing playing a game based
on rumors with no basis in reality. So,
get this [__] You climb on the
elevator, then you press 4, 2, 6, 2, 10,
and 5. And on the fifth floor, she gets
on. Who gets on? The mirror without a
face. If you look at her, she'll steal
your soul and spank you. That's kind of
sexy. No, it's stupid. There's no logic
behind their claims at all. Just vague
superstitions and fantasies of wanting
to be spanked. Twilight is right. You
girls are nuttier than a bag of nuts.
Ain't no faceless m going around
spanking [__]
Good luck, Applejack. Don't talk to the
faceless lady.
Oh my god. Hey, Applejack. How about a
parting gift for good luck?
Uh-oh. Stinky. Haha. My booty is stinky.
Oh my god, Pinkie Pie, you're so
strange. Haha, she's got Applejack
trapped in the elevator and she's
filling it up like it's a gas chamber.
God, I wish that was me. Don't touch my
butt. Well, I can't close the elevator
door with your huge ass in the way. He
Sorry.
Hi, miss. Where is your face?
Applejack's soul has been claimed. Lost
in the cursed dimension between floors
10 and 5. Detox time. Detox time. Detox.
Check it, girls. There's a waffle
convention going on downstairs. I
literally don't care. It's time for our
first agreed upon activity. As per the
rules, each of us were able to bring one
item from the outside world into this
room. And maybe one extra special item
for a very special girl. No butter
shits, just one item. I brought a
portable toilet so we can put it by the
window and poop while looking out the
window. We will make good use of that.
Next, I brought this box of granola
bars. That box clearly says there's 18,
you little [__] The rules are that we
can only bring one thing anymore, and it
would totally defeat the point of a
social detox. I'm afraid I'm going to
have to confiscate at least 17 of
those. I brought a book, How to Share a
Hotel Room with Five Other Idiots. You
brought homework to our vacation. I
brought order and structure. I brought a
bottle of [__] I mean lotion to rub all
over my naked body. I like to be
moisturized even when I'm surrounded by
ponies who don't deserve me at my best.
We will make good use of that next. I
brought a limited time only pretzel
crust pizza from Little Kzers and a can
of their brand new Mango Rush Mountain
Dew flavor that we can all share.
Fluttershy, you already brought a party
hat, which means the pizza would count
as 2 through nine since pizzas on
average come in eight slices. And you
also have the audacity to bring a drink,
so that would be 10. I'm afraid I'm
going to have to confiscate your items
as well.
Uh, give that to me. Give it,
Fluttershy. Give that to me.
How much did the mango drink cost? 299.
I think it's not very good. You should
get your money back. Why can't you just
rank it, fat ass?
I think someone is at the door. Should I
go see who it is? No. Pinkie Pie will
answer the door. The rest of us will
remain exactly as we are. Why do I have
to? Because I said so.
We're here for the party. Move. Yay.
Yeah, it's my sisters. Hi, Marble. Hi,
Limestone. Oh, hey. Hey,
M. Hi, Pinkie
Pie. We're here for that lame ass
birthday party you told us about girly
goo. Move your party balloons a ka your
massive butt cheeks out of the way
before I spread them. And so, um, how
have you been since leaving the rock
farm? Well, I haven't been collecting
rocks. Haha. Looks like we got ourselves
a wise cracker here. Which is weird
because unless I'm mentally challenged
like you are Pinkie Pie, you're neither
wise or a cracker. The only cracks I
expect to see from you for the rest of
the day is your butt crack. And only on
my time when I say it. No, I just don't
like collecting rocks. Hold on. I'm
confused. Every horse likes collecting
rocks. It's literally what life is for.
Calm down, Limestone. We made our life
choices. She made hers. Even if it is
the wrong one. I am not going to let you
try to gaslight me into thinking I like
rocks. Lawn stone, not in front of my
friends. Gaslighting? Sweetie, if I
wanted to gaslight you, you'd be begging
to come back and fondle my massive
rocks. Look, Lstone, no pony is trying
to take away your rock goddess title.
Say that again. No, I will not. I refuse
to become a part of your ever growing
ego limestone pie. I understand that you
think rocks are cool, but that doesn't
give you the right to go around telling
ponies they should spend their whole
lives stacking rocks. You Yes, it does.
Limestone, can you let me finish my
sentences? Why do you always interrupt
me? Because all you ever want to talk
about is making people smile and
bringing about world peace. You never
ever have anything important to say.
Hey, Pinkie Pie. I've been organizing my
rock collection if you want to see. I
don't really want to. Well, can I just
show it to you anyway?
Fine, Ma. Never mind. I'll just take my
rocks home. Wait, why? I wouldn't want
to waste your time. It's obvious you
don't want to with that reaction. I want
to see it. I'm not mad at you. It's just
the situation. You know what I mean?
These are currently the top four in my
collection. If you have any questions,
don't be afraid to stop me. I'm not
going to ask any questions. This one is
my favorite. What kind of weather do you
think it's been in that caused these
markings? Oh, I didn't really know you
were going to turn this into a
discussion. I'm going back inside and
play with my friends.
I'm getting hungry. Who wants to go
downstairs to the waffle convention? No,
we're going to stay in this room and eat
below knee and cheese sandwiches. How do
we know those waffles downstairs weren't
sourced from another locations outside
of this specific hotel? I don't want to
eat baloney knee and cheese sandwiches.
I want real food. Fine, if you're that
desperate, I'll give you a couple
quarters so you can buy a packet of
cookies or something from the vending
machine out in the hall. Just don't let
me see them. I'm on a diet and I'm a
little piggy when it comes to thin
mints.
Look, [__] the waffle convention is
in full swing. Yay!
They're really decorating those waffles
like it's no pony's business. So So
let's go in and get some. Look, the sign
even says free. No. Wowee. They have
fruits and berries and everything. You
know what also has fruits and berries?
Granola bars, which can be found in some
vending machines. Maybe even the one in
this
hotel. Put the money in. I haven't
decided what I wanted yet. You said you
wanted those ultrarocessed chocolate
discs with the cream in the middle.
Yeah, but now I have options to choose
from. Also, the Oreos are 2.75. I can't
afford that crap with what you gave me.
Get Fun Yuns. What even are fun yans?
I don't know, but I think the fusion of
the words fun and onion are really
clever and silly. Put the money in. We
don't got all day. We have to get back
to the room before Pinkie Pie breaks
something. I'm trying, but the stupid
dollar you gave me is like a wrinkled
ball sack.
Help me. I can't feel my legs.
It's too heavy. With all the granola
bars and cans of soda, I can't lift it
even with my magic. I don't want to die
here.
When you farted, it bounced a little
bit. Try farting again. Fart if you want
to live. Still not working. I'm afraid
you're stuck. I'm going to go back to
the room and see if I can find something
to leverage under the vending machine.
Yo, Pinky Piss, toss me the remote.
[__]
darling, I'm sorry, but I need to go
poop. Rarity, please don't leave me too.
You can't like tell me what to do.
What would Princess Celestia think if
she found out her prized student was
found dead under a vending machine all
alone? Think about it. I don't want to
stop trying to make everything about
you. Have you ever stopped to think that
maybe this is karma for making us try to
do everything your way or the highway?
Also, I kind of want to go to the waffle
convention since I'm sure that's where
Rainbow Dash is headed now. [__] that's
smart. I'm sure they have ladles and
pots and pans we can use to wedge under
the vending machine. Yeah, that's the
reason I want to go.
Oh, Twilight, my own student found
herself stuck under a vending machine.
How humiliating,
Fluttershy, I think I have some clue why
you're feeling so down. You're sad
because you think no pony realized it's
a girl's very special day. Is that it?
Well, let me tell you something, girl.
They didn't forget.
Birthday to
you. Happy
birthday to
birthday,
dear. Happy
birthday to you.
Oh, girls, you really, really shouldn't
have. This is so This is the sweetest
thing any pony's ever done for me. Thank
you, girls. I thought you all forgot.
Now, how could we forget the birthday of
the most bombastic [__] of bimbo on
this side of the block? Hurry and slice
the vegan cake already. Birthday girl,
I'm getting hungry.
Wow, it's lemon. That's my favorite. You
girls know me so well. Yo, Fluttershy,
you want a slice? I know how much you
like lemons.
She's lying. It's not her birthday. It's
mine. She's just trying to get back at
me. Golly, Fluttershy. Not everything
has to be about you. Yeah. Do you really
think Pinkie Pie would hold a grudge?
Don't ruin Pinkie Pie's special day.
Aha. It's okay, girls. And Rainbow Dash
is right. No, I'm blue. I'm totally over
how you ruined my lemonade stand. Took a
day out of my life by stealing my
customers. But if you really want me to
share my birthday with you, I will.
Because unlike most, I'm a very nice
pony. No, it's mine. Mine. Mine. Mine.
No, it's not. Now, put on this bikini
and dance for the birthday girl like
it's the end of the world. As you do for
all of our birthday parties. Fine, but
only with Pinkie Pie. And it has to be
alone in the bathroom.
All right, get dancing, [__] I want to
see it jiggle wiggle.
I'm going to make you my [__] I think
they're having sex.
Drink my dirty eleus. Drink
it. Put a tone. You're going to be the
one shaking those fats for me now,
[__] Do it. Dance for me, [__] Shake
those sweaty boobies in my face.
Fluttershy, what in Equestria is up with
you? Have you gone mad? Send her back to
meet Twilight. She's still being a salty
[__] about the lemonade. Lemonade?
Look, look at the cake. It's lemon.
Pinkie Pie doesn't even like lemon. This
isn't lemon. This is chocolate. She's
delusional. You know what? Every pony, I
think we should kick Fluttershy out of
our friend group. No, girls. That would
be a terrible thing to do to her. Even
if she does deserve it, I'll be fine
with a teeny tiny apology.
Fluttershy, will you apologize to me so
that I may forgive you? A Pinkie Pie is
so sweet. Yeah, Fluttershy, you should
feel grateful that Pinkie Pie is even
giving you a second chance. Hurry up and
apologize to her already. I'm sorry. You
did a terrible thing today, Fluttershy.
I hope you know that.
Sup, everyone. I'm Todd Sparkle and I'm
here to show you the world famous
Sparkle family recipe for waffles.
Complete original waffle mix, some
vegetable oil, some good old maps, and
some butter and some water to like make
the waffles and [__] Now, the
measurements are very easy. You just see
like one cup of like the waffle mix. So,
I'm going to add that to bowl right now.
And you're going to have need about one
cup of water. So I can I'm not really
better cuz I don't really need to. So
can add that. And we're going to have to
And you're going to mix that [__] So
mix it all
up. I'm I'm going to add a little bit
more. Just enough that it's like thick
as my [__]
All
right, Sako fans know what I
mean. Okay, as you can see, it's it's
completely mixed in there. And now we're
going to have to put this on the
parchment paper. Are you following? Are
you following me? Now, this is
about This is This is the good [__]
When you stop making the [__] waffle
and you got to be be careful not to make
a mess. I don't I don't make
messes. Get that microwave
ready. And now what you're going to want
to do after it's like ready to go in,
you got to set it for 2 minutes.
Anything more, it'll burn. Anything
less, you're not going to have a [__]
waffle.
Now
this this is the fun part where you it's
time to get creative. Butter and map
soap combination. So that's what I'm
going to go with. So I got
my got my stick of butter here.
Gonna cut that
[__] and put it on. Now just drown that
[__]